{"1": {"question": "What is the art song set work?", "correct": "O Mistress Mine from Let Us Garlands Bring Op.18 ", "incorrect": ["O Mistress Mine from Garlands Let Us Take Op.81 ", "Airplane, Pt.2 by BTS (highly recommend)", "O Mistress Mine from Let Us Bring Garlands Op.28 "]}, "2": {"question": "Who wrote the text of Let Us Garlands Bring?", "correct": "Shakespeare", "incorrect": ["Hitman Bang", "Milton", "Coleridge"]}, "3": {"question": "How many separate texts does Let Us Garlands Bring set?", "correct": "Five", "incorrect": ["Thirteen", "Eight", "Eleven"]}, "4": {"question": "Which of the following was NOT a composer of art song?", "correct": "[lieder composer]", "incorrect": ["Ralph Vaughan Williams", "John Ireland", "Arnold Bax"]}, "5": {"question": "What is O Mistress Mine about?", "correct": "It is a light-hearted reflection on love and youth.", "incorrect": ["It is a deep reflection on love and the mortality of youth.", "It is a light-hearted reflection on being grateful for little things.", "It is about waiting for 00:00 when the day will be over"]}, "6": {"question": "What was the 'English musical Renaissance'?", "correct": "The period in which England freed themselves from foreign musical influences, to have begun writing in a distinctively national manner", "incorrect": ["The period in which England freed themselves from old national English music and changed their style.", "The period in which English composers competed against BTS as to who could write better songs, and BTS won.", "The period in which England was overwhelmed by foreign musical influences and lost their national musical style."]}, "7": {"question": "Who wrote the art song set work?", "correct": "Gerald Finzi", "incorrect": ["Franz Schubert", "George Friedric Handel", "Rapmon"]}, "8": {"question": "What is the rhyme scheme of each sextain in Let Us Garlands Bring?", "correct": "AABCCB", "incorrect": ["ABACDC", "AAABBB", "ABBCBB"]}, "9": {"question": "Finzi - How are the modulations in the piece used to reflect the ideas in the text?", "correct": "The piece is bouncy as the poet addresses the object of his affection, and becomes more reflective as the poet addresses the need to be joyful while still young.", "incorrect": ["The song is determined as the idea of surviving one more day is expressed, and is temporarily taken back a notch as though building up energy to explode. ", "The piece is more reflective as the poet addresses the object of his affection, and becomes bouncy as the poet addresses the need to be joyful while still young.", "The piece is slow and melancholy as the poet addresses the once-was object of his affection, and becomes reflective as he addresses the need to be joyful while still young."]}, "10": {"question": "Finzi - What does the text consist of?", "correct": "Two six-line stanzas or sextains", "incorrect": ["Three six-line stanzas or sextains", "Six four-line stanzas or quatrains", "Hobicore vibes"]}, "11": {"question": "What is the role of the piano in O Mistress Mine?", "correct": "It sets up the general feeling in the introduction and remains remarkably consistent in mood, supporting the vocal part.", "incorrect": ["It is accompanied by the vocal part"]}, "12": {"question": "Which play is the text of Let Us Garlands Bring from?", "correct": "Twelfth Night by Shakespeare", "incorrect": ["Twelfth Day by Shakespeare", "Ninth Night by Shakespeare", "Life Goes On by BTS"]}, "13": {"question": "Finzi - How is the vocal line?", "correct": "Simple and direct", "incorrect": ["Extravagant and indirect", "Excessively simple", "Straightfoward and monotonous"]}, "14": {"question": "Finzi - How is the text set?", "correct": "Syllabic and has a natural rhythm close to the declamation of the words.", "incorrect": ["Melismatic and has a rhythm not very close to the declamation of the words.", "Melismatic but has a natural rhythm close to the declamation of the words.", "Syllabic but has a rhythm not very close to the declamation of the words."]}, "15": {"question": "How does Finzi emphasise the point of the text?", "correct": "By using direct imitation between the voice and the piano at the final line of each stanza", "incorrect": ["By using direct imitation between the voice and the piano at the final line of the piece", "By using direct imitation between the voice and the piano of motifs throughout the piece", "By using direct imitation between the voice and the piano at the first line of each stanza"]}, "16": {"question": "Finzi - What key does the harmony shift to at the final line of each stanza?", "correct": "The parallel minor", "incorrect": ["The dominant", "The relative minor", "The parallel major"]}, "17": {"question": "Finzi - What is the form of the song?", "correct": "Semi-strophic", "incorrect": ["Modified strophic", "Simple strophic", "Binary"]}, "18": {"question": "Finzi - What are the stanzas framed by?", "correct": "A piano inroduction, interlude and postlude", "incorrect": ["A piano introduction, interlude and voice+piano postlude", "A voice+piano introduction, interlude and postlude", "A voice introduction, voice+piano interlude, voice postlude"]}, "19": {"question": "Finzi - What key is the piece in?", "correct": "E flat major", "incorrect": ["A flat major", "E major", "F major"]}, "20": {"question": "What key does O Mistress Mine modulate to?", "correct": "It does not modulate", "incorrect": ["C minor", "The parallel minor", "G minor"]}, "21": {"question": "Finzi - How is the melody written?", "correct": "Mostly diatonic except for the end of each stanza where a modal mixture is introduced", "incorrect": ["Mostly chromatic except for the end of each stanza where it becomes diatonic", "All diatonic", "Mostly diatonic except for the end of the piece where a modal mixture is introduced"]}, "22": {"question": "Finzi - What is the mood of the piece?", "correct": "Light-hearted and jaunty but becomes more reflective as modal mixture is introduced", "incorrect": ["Reflective but becomes more light-hearted and jaunty as modal mixture is introduced", "Light-hearted and jaunty", "Reflective"]}, "23": {"question": "Which syllables does Finzi ensure land on the first beat of the bar?", "correct": "Stressed", "incorrect": ["Unstressed", "Both", "jUst rAndOm syLLaBLeS"]}, "24": {"question": "Finzi - Where are the only instances of direct imitation found?", "correct": "At the end of each stanza between the voice and the piano", "incorrect": ["At the beginning of each stanza between the voice and the piano", "There are no instances of direct imitation in the piece", "At the end of the piece between the voice and the piano"]}, "25": {"question": "Finzi - Describe the texture of the accompaniment at the end of the each stanza.", "correct": "Legato articulation and longer note values, slower pace, and dramatic contrast of dynamics.", "incorrect": ["Staccato articulation and shorter note values, faster pace, no contrast of dynamics.", "Legato articulation and longer note values, slower pace, less contrast of dynamics.", "Legato articulation and shorter note values, slower pace and dramatic contrast of dynamics."]}, "26": {"question": "Finzi - Describe the cadence at the end of each stanza?", "correct": "It is joined with the commencement of the next piano section (interlude/postlude)", "incorrect": ["It is separated from the next piano section (interlude/postlude)", "It is joined with the commencement of the next stanza", "It is joined with a four-bar outro of sorts before the interlude/postlude commences"]}, "27": {"question": "Finzi - In what way is the piece flexible and natural?", "correct": "The voice sets the text differently in each stanza while the accompaniment stays the same.", "incorrect": ["The accompaniment is different in each stanza while the voice stays the same.", "The voice sets the text differently in each stanza, just like the accompaniment.", "The voice and accompaniment stay the same, but rubato and ornaments are used."]}, "28": {"question": "Generally, what is the role of the Piano in Art songs?", "correct": "Shares prominence with the vocal part", "incorrect": ["Secondary to the vocal part", "Ternary to the vocal part", "Primary above the vocal part", "Quaternary to the vocal part"]}, "29": {"question": "Let us garlands bring is a set of how many songs?", "correct": "Five", "incorrect": ["Thirteen", "Eight", "Eleven"]}, "30": {"question": "What does Allegretto amabile mean?", "correct": "Moderately fast and pleasant", "incorrect": ["Not too fast and pleasant", "Very fast and unpleasant", "Walking pace and pleasant"]}, "31": {"question": "Finzi - Which of the following is NOT a stylistic characteristic of the song?", "correct": "Use of raised 7th notes in minor keys", "incorrect": ["Some dissonance and occasional use of parallel 5ths to the bass", "Irregular phrase lengths and syncopation and changes of meter", "Angular melodies (at times)"]}, "32": {"question": "What does sempre staccato mean?", "correct": "Always detached", "incorrect": ["Never detached", "The Ravenswood magazine", "Very detached"]}, "33": {"question": "Finzi - What key is the piano part in?", "correct": "E flat major", "incorrect": ["E flat minor", "A major", "A minor"]}, "34": {"question": "Which of the following techniques does Finzi NOT use in the song?", "correct": "Chromatic harmony", "incorrect": ["Imitation", "Counterpoint", "Diatonic harmony"]}, "35": {"question": "What kind of techniques does Finzi deliberately use in the song?", "correct": "Techniques associated with earlier music styles from Shakespeare's time", "incorrect": ["Techniques ahead of Finzi's time", "Techniques associated with earlier styles such as Classical", "Techniques associated with Kpop"]}, "36": {"question": "Finzi - What is the underlying message of the song?", "correct": "To seize life's joys and pleasures while you can", "incorrect": ["To be yourself", "To pursue your dreams", "To listen to BTS"]}, "37": {"question": "Finzi - Which of the following is NOT part of the change in texture at the end of each stanza?", "correct": "Faster", "incorrect": ["Broader", "Denser", "Slower"]}, "38": {"question": "Finzi - Who is the piece sung by?", "correct": "Feste, the jester in the court of Countess Olivia", "incorrect": ["Countess Olivia, to her jester, Feste", "Feste, the brother of Countess Olivia", "Feste, the father of Countess Olivia"]}}